# **FAROUK AHMED**

Nairobi, Kenya | thiaqoacookie@gmail.com | www.faroukahmed.com

### **PROFILE**

I'm a self taught frontend developer from Nairobi, Kenya with a passion for web development. I have 1 year of experience, I'm a good colleague who loves getting the best out of everyone I'm working with and also I'm fluent in English and Kiswahili is my Native Language. I'm keen to pursue a career in web development with a focus on the frontend part of it.

## **SKILLS**

Languages
Javascript, HTML, CSS
Frameworks and Libraries
Bootstrap and Sass
Technologies
Git and Wordpress

### **EXPERIENCE**

Freelance software developer. January 2022 - Present

Currently on exciting freelance projects with clients globally which is helping me solidify my skills and making me gain valuable experience. (HTML, CSS, Javascript Bootstrap and Sass).

**Software Developer and Digital Marketing - Amazon Cellular** (Nairobi, Kenya). June 2020 - December 2021

Implemented the layout and functionality of an ecommerce web app . The web app was integrated with Google Analytics and Facebook Pixel which were useful in selling electronics countrywide (Kenya) which I was handling too.(HTML, CSS, Javascript Bootstrap and Sass)

### **EDUCATION**

Railway Training Institute. Feb 2019 - July 2021